Guide to the Washington State Federation of Teachers Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
Washington State Federation of Teachers records
1937-2006
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
2201
Washington State Federation of Teachers
22.39 cubic feet
Correspondence, reports, speeches and ephemera related to teachers' union of Washington state
The Washington State Federation of Teachers was formed in the mid-1930s when several American Federation of Teachers local union affiliates joined together and formed the Washington Joint Council of Teachers, soon reorganized as the WSFT. The Federation and its affiliates organized K-12 teachers throughout the state, but had the most success in western Washington, with a collective bargaining agreement in Bremerton public schools in the late 1930s and strength in secondary schools elsewhere. Later the union organized successfully among community college faculty. By the 1980s most K-12 teacher organizing had been abandoned in the face of successful collective bargaining by National Education Organization affiliates. Today (2016) the organization represents pre-K through 12 classified staff, and professional staff in community and technical colleges. The organization's name was changed to Washington Federation of Teachers in the 1980s, and to AFT Washington in the 2000s.
Organized into 8 accessions.
Accession No. 2201-001, Washington State Federation of Teachers records, 1937-2006
Accession No. 2201-002, Washington State Federation of Teachers records, 1962-1972
Accession No. 2201-003, Washington State Federation of Teachers records, circa 1968-1972
Accession No. 2201-004, Washington State Federation of Teachers records, 1952-1980
Accession No. 2201-005, Washington State Federation of Teachers records, 1969-1978
Accession No. 2201-006, Washington State Federation of Teachers records, 1950-1978
Accession No. 2201-007, Washington State Federation of Teachers records, 1970-1985
Accession No. 2201-008, Washington State Federation of Teachers records, 1947-2006
Organizational records, including constitutions, minutes of the union's executive board (1945-2002) and councils of the federation; administrative records; correspondence (1949-2002), convention and conference records (1945-2005). Subject files (1943-2006) deal largely with organizing, collective bargaining and political issues but include substantial material related to the activities of local union affiliates. Legal records include case files related to representation and grievance cases. Publications include newsletters of the WSFT and of groups within it and of affiliates. Related to the publication files is a series of records, daily filings (1969-1979), that consists of a chronological file of materials duplicated by the WSFT office for distribution to affiliates, including newsletters and circulars and publications produced for the state federation's affiliated local unions. Records of several affiliated organizations are also included in these records, including records of the Bremerton Federation of Teachers, AFT Local 336 (1935-1965); Lake Washington Federation of Teachers, AFT Local 2298 (1970-1972); Seattle Federation of Teachers, AFT Local 200 (1951-1972); and Seattle Community College Federation of Teachers, AFT Local 1789 (1970-1973).
Creator's literary rights transferred to the University of Washington Libraries.
The Elmer Miller Papers, Accession No. 1086-001, contain substantial material related to the WSFT, especially for the period 1935-1966, including correspondence, Executive Board minutes, and convention records. Miller was active in leadership of the WSFT from its beginning and in the predecessor organization, the Washington Joint Council of Teachers.
Brisbois, Alfred K.; Graves, H. D.; Johnson, Ralph Whitney,$d1923-; Paschal, Harold; Miller, Elmer; Rieder, Ross K.; American Federation of Teachers.$bLocal 2298 (Kirkland, Wash.); American Federation of Teachers.$bLocal 1789 (Seattle, Wash.); American Federation of Teachers.$bLocal 200 (Seattle, Wash.); American Federation of Teachers.$bLocal 772 (Everett, Wash.); American Federation of Teachers.$bLocal 336 (Bremerton, Wash.); Washington Education Association; Washington State Federation of Labor; Washington State Federation of Teachers.$bCollege and University Council; Washington State Federation of Teachers.$bExecutive Board; Washington State Federation of Teachers.$bK-12 Council; Washington State Federation of Teachers.$bPresident; Washington State Federation of Teachers.$bRetired Teachers' Federation; Washington State Federation of Teachers$vArchives; Washington State Federation of Teachers$xMembership; Washington State Federation of Teachers$xFinance; Washington State Federation of Teachers$xEmployees; American Federation of Teachers; Labor Archives of Washington (University of Washington); Washington (State)$xPolitics and government; Teachers' unions$zWashington (State)$vArchives; Teachers' unions$vCongresses; Lobbying$zWashington (State); Education$zWashington (State); Educational law and legislation$zWashington (State); Newsletters; Business correspondence; Records (Documents); Minutes (Records); Ephemera.; Records and briefs; Conference materials; Collective labor agreements; Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Labor History; Labor Unions; Elementary and Secondary Education; Colleges and Universities; Washington (State)
- Washington State Federation of Teachers records, 1937-2006; 2201-001; 20 cubic feet (20 boxes)
  Organizational records, including constitutions, minutes of the union's executive board (1945-2002) and councils of the federation; administrative records; correspondence (1949-2002), convention and conference records (1945-2005). Subject files (1943-2006) deal largely with organizing, collective bargaining and political issues but include substantial material related to the activities of local union affiliates. Legal records include case files related to representation and grievance cases. Publications include newsletters of the WSFT and of groups within it and of affiliates. Related to the publication files is a series of records, daily filings (1969-1979), that consists of a chronological file of materials duplicated by the WSFT office for distribution to affiliates, including newsletters and circulars and publications produced for the state federation's affiliated local unions. Records of several affiliated organizations are also included in these records, including records of the Bremerton Federation of Teachers, AFT Local 336 (1935-1965); Lake Washington Federation of Teachers, AFT Local 2298 (1970-1972); Seattle Federation of Teachers, AFT Local 200 (1951-1972); and Seattle Community College Federation of Teachers, AFT Local 1789 (1970-1973).
  Open to all users.
  Records stored offsite; advance notice required for use.
  Donated by Frank N. Morris, 2/10/1969.
  - WASHINGTON STATE FEDERATION OF TEACHERS RECORDS, RECORD GROUP 1 (Box-folder 1/1-20/2)
    - ORGANIZATIONAL RECORDS, 1935-2002; SERIES I (Box-folder 1/1-1/12)
      - Constitution, 1970-1987 (Box-folder 1/1)
      - Constitution, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 1/2)
      - Constitution, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 1/3)
      - Constitution, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 1/4)
      - Constitution, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 1/5)
      - Constitution, 2005 (Box-folder 1/6)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers history, 1935 (Box-folder 1/7)
      - Membership and officer lists, Undated, 1947-1974 (Box-folder 1/8)
      - Membership lists, 1964-1968 (Box-folder 1/9)
      - Membership summaries, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 1/10)
      - Membership reports, 1993 (Box-folder 1/11)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers local officers, 1991-2000 (Box-folder 1/12)
    - MINUTES, 1945-2002; SERIES II (Box-folder 1/13-2/31)
      - Executive Board minutes, 1945-1948 (Box-folder 1/13)
      - Executive Board minutes, 1953 (Box-folder 1/14)
      - Executive Board minutes, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 1/15)
      - Executive Board minutes, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 1/16)
      - Executive Board minutes, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 1/17)
      - Executive Board minutes, 1972 (Box-folder 1/18)
      - Executive Board minutes, 1973 (Box-folder 1/19)
      - Executive Board minutes -- Part 1 of 2, 1974 (Box-folder 1/20)
      - Executive Board minutes -- Part 2 of 2, 1974 (Box-folder 1/21)
      - Executive Board minutes -- Part 1 of 3, 1975 (Box-folder 1/22)
      - Executive Board minutes -- Part 2 of 3, 1975 (Box-folder 1/23)
      - Executive Board minutes -- Part 3 of 3, 1975 (Box-folder 1/24)
      - Executive Board minutes -- Part 1 of 2, 1976 (Box-folder 1/25)
      - Executive Board minutes -- Part 2 of 3, 1976 (Box-folder 1/26)
      - Executive Board minutes -- Part 3 of 3, 1976 (Box-folder 1/27)
      - Executive Board minutes -- Part 1 of 2, 1977 (Box-folder 1/28)
      - Executive Board minutes -- Part 2 of 2, 1977 (Box-folder 1/29)
      - Executive Board minutes -- Part 1 of 2, 1978 (Box-folder 2/1)
      - Executive Board minutes -- Part 2 of 2, 1978 (Box-folder 2/2)
      - Executive Board minutes -- Part 1 of 2, 1979 (Box-folder 2/3)
      - Executive Board minutes -- Part 2 of 3, 1979 (Box-folder 2/4)
      - Executive Board minutes -- Part 3 of 3, 1979 (Box-folder 2/5)
      - Executive Board minutes, 1985 (Box-folder 2/6)
      - Executive Board minutes, 1986 (Box-folder 2/7)
      - Executive Board minutes, 1989 (Box-folder 2/8)
      - Executive Board minutes, 1990 (Box-folder 2/9)
      - Executive Board minutes, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 2/10)
      - Executive Board minutes, 1993 (Box-folder 2/11)
      - Executive Board minutes, 1994 (Box-folder 2/12)
      - Executive Board minutes, 1995 (Box-folder 2/13)
      - Executive Board minutes, 1996 (Box-folder 2/14)
      - Executive Board minutes, 1997 (Box-folder 2/15)
      - Executive Board minutes -- Part 1 of 2, 1998 (Box-folder 2/16)
      - Executive Board minutes -- Part 2 of 2, 1998 (Box-folder 2/17)
      - Executive Board minutes, 1999 (Box-folder 2/18)
      - Executive Board minutes, 2000 (Box-folder 2/19)
      - Executive Board minutes, 2001 (Box-folder 2/20)
      - Executive Board minutes, 2002 (Box-folder 2/21)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers College and University Council minutes, 1979 (Box-folder 2/22)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers Community College Council minutes, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 2/23)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers Community College Council minutes, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 2/24)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers Community College Council minutes, 1994 (Box-folder 2/25)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers Community College Council minutes, 1995 (Box-folder 2/26)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers Community College Council minutes, 1996 (Box-folder 2/27)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers Community College Council minutes, 1997 (Box-folder 2/28)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers K-12 Council minutes, 1979 (Box-folder 2/29)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers Part-time Caucus minutes, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 2/30)
      - Minutes of affiliated locals, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 2/31)
    - ADMINISTRATIVE RECORDS, 1969-2004; SERIES III (Box-folder 3/1-3/17)
      - Ross Rieder contract, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 3/1)
      - John Barton contract, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 3/2)
      - Al Brisbois contract and reports, 1975-1985 (Box-folder 3/3)
      - Evelyn Rieder, 1989 (Box-folder 3/4)
      - Susan Levy, 1997 (Box-folder 3/5)
      - Employment contracts, 1975 (Box-folder 3/6)
      - Field representative contract and reports, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 3/7)
      - Field representative contract and reports, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 3/8)
      - Legislative Advocacy contract and reports, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 3/9)
      - Staff issues and responsibilities, 1998 (Box-folder 3/10)
      - Staff issues and policies, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 3/11)
      - Staff issues, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 3/12)
      - Staff meeting and planning, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 3/13)
      - Office and Professional Employees Local No. 8, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 3/14)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers agreement with American Federation of Teachers/Washington Staff Union, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 3/15)
      - Organizational Records, 2001 (Box-folder 3/16)
      - Grievances, 1991 (Box-folder 3/17)
    - FINANCIAL RECORDS, 1951-2004; SERIES IV (Box-folder 3/18-3/37)
      - Reports and records, 1957 (Box-folder 3/18)
      - Reports and records, 1970 (Box-folder 3/19)
      - Reports and records, 1971 (Box-folder 3/20)
      - Reports and records, Undated (Box-folder 3/21)
      - Treasurer's reports, 1951-1953 (Box-folder 3/22)
      - Treasurer's reports, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 3/23)
      - Financial reports, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 3/24)
      - Financial reports, 1992 (Box-folder 3/25)
      - Financial statements, 2004 (Box-folder 3/26)
      - Ledger, 1947-1952 (Box-folder 3/27)
      - Ledger, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 3/28)
      - Ledger, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 3/29)
      - Ledger, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 3/30)
      - Budget, 1975 (Box-folder 3/31)
      - Financial correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 3/32)
      - Per capita correspondence, 1968-1976 (Box-folder 3/33)
      - Organizing fund, 1970 (Box-folder 3/34)
      - Expense records, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 3/35)
      - Payroll information, 1969 (Box-folder 3/36)
      - FICA / IRS reports, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 3/37)
    - CORRESPONDENCE, 1949-2002; SERIES V
      - INCOMING CORRESPONDENCE, 1949-1972; SUBSERIES I (Box-folder 3/38-4/37)
        - A, 1965-1972 (Box-folder 3/38)
        - Bassett, Donaldson & Hafer, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 3/39)
        - Hilde Birnbaum, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 3/40)
        - Stewart Bledsoe, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 3/41)
        - B, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 3/42)
        - C, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 3/43)
        - D, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 3/44)
        - Everett Education Association, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 3/45)
        - Everett Public Schools, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 3/46)
        - E, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 3/47)
        - F, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 3/48)
        - G, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 3/49)
        - H, 1964-1972 (Box-folder 3/50)
        - I, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 3/51)
        - J, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 3/52)
        - K, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 3/53)
        - L, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 3/54)
        - MacDonald, Hoague & Bayless, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 3/55)
        - M, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 3/56)
        - N, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 3/57)
        - O, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 3/58)
        - P, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 3/59)
        - R, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 3/60)
        - David R. Sprague, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 3/61)
        - S, 1965-1972 (Box-folder 3/62)
        - American Federation of Teachers, 1964-1972 (Box-folder 4/1)
        - American Federation of Teachers. Civil Rights Department, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 4/2)
        - American Federation of Teachers. President, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 4/3)
        - American Federation of Teachers. Research Department, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 4/4)
        - American Federation of Teachers. Secretary-Treasurer, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 4/5)
        - American Federation of Teachers. State Federations Department, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 4/6)
        - American Federation of Teachers. California, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 4/7)
        - American Federation of Teachers. Colorado-Oregon, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 4/8)
        - American Federation of Teachers. Washington, 1964-1971 (Box-folder 4/9)
        - American Federation of Teachers. Aberdeen, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 4/10)
        - American Federation of Teachers. Bremerton Local 336, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 4/11)
        - American Federation of Teachers. Everett Local 772, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 4/12)
        - American Federation of Teachers. Green River Community College, Undated, c. 1972 (Box-folder 4/13)
        - American Federation of Teachers. Hoquiam Local 1982, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 4/14)
        - American Federation of Teachers. Olympia Local 478, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 4/15)
        - American Federation of Teachers. Port Angeles Local 793, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 4/16)
        - American Federation of Teachers. Renton Local 2020, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 4/17)
        - American Federation of Teachers. Seattle Local 200, 1949-1972 (Box-folder 4/18)
        - American Federation of Teachers. Seattle Community College Local 1789, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 4/19)
        - American Federation of Teachers. Shoreline Community College Local 1950, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 4/20)
        - American Federation of Teachers. Spokane Local 987, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 4/21)
        - American Federation of Teachers. Tacoma Local 461, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 4/22)
        - T, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 4/23)
        - U-V, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 4/24)
        - Washington Community College Board, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 4/25)
        - Central Washington College, 1965 (Box-folder 4/26)
        - Eastern Washington State College, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 4/27)
        - Washington. Governor, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 4/28)
        - Washington Legislature Interim Committee on Education, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 4/29)
        - Washington Legislature Joint Committee on Education, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 4/30)
        - Washington. Temporary Special Levy Study Commission, 1970 (Box-folder 4/31)
        - Washington Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 4/32)
        - Washington State University, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 4/33)
        - Washington State government, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 4/34)
        - Washington State Labor Council, 1965-1972 (Box-folder 4/35)
        - Washington Education Association, 1962-1971 (Box-folder 4/36)
        - W, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 4/37)
      - OUTGOING CORRESPONDENCE, 1965-1972; SUBSERIES II (Box-folder 4/38-4/45)
        - 1965 (Box-folder 4/38)
        - 1966 (Box-folder 4/39)
        - 1967 (Box-folder 4/40)
        - 1968 (Box-folder 4/41)
        - 1969 (Box-folder 4/42)
        - 1970 (Box-folder 4/43)
        - 1971 (Box-folder 4/44)
        - 1972 (Box-folder 4/45)
      - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE, 1969-2002; SUBSERIES III (Box-folder 4/46-6/26)
        - Rieder correspondence -- Part 1 of 4, 1969 (Box-folder 4/46)
        - Rieder correspondence -- Part 2 of 4, 1969 (Box-folder 4/47)
        - Rieder correspondence -- Part 3 of 4, 1969 (Box-folder 4/48)
        - Rieder correspondence -- Part 4 of 4, 1969 (Box-folder 4/49)
        - Rieder correspondence -- Part 1 of 3, 1972 (Box-folder 5/1)
        - Rieder correspondence -- Part 2 of 3, 1972 (Box-folder 5/2)
        - Rieder correspondence -- Part 3 of 3, 1972 (Box-folder 5/3)
        - A-B, 1973 (Box-folder 5/4)
        - C-F, 1973 (Box-folder 5/5)
        - G-K, 1973 (Box-folder 5/6)
        - L-P, 1973 (Box-folder 5/7)
        - R-Z, 1973 (Box-folder 5/8)
        - A-B, 1974 (Box-folder 5/9)
        - C-F, 1974 (Box-folder 5/10)
        - E-L, 1974 (Box-folder 5/11)
        - M-P, 1974 (Box-folder 5/12)
        - R-S, 1974 (Box-folder 5/13)
        - T-Z, 1974 (Box-folder 5/14)
        - A-B, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 5/15)
        - C-E, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 5/16)
        - F-G, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 5/17)
        - H-J, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 5/18)
        - K-L, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 5/19)
        - M, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 5/20)
        - N-R, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 5/21)
        - S, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 5/22)
        - T-Z, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 5/23)
        - General correspondence -- Part 1 of 4, 1976 (Box-folder 6/1)
        - General correspondence -- Part 2 of 4, 1976 (Box-folder 6/2)
        - General correspondence -- Part 3 of 4, 1976 (Box-folder 6/3)
        - General correspondence -- Part 4 of 4, 1976 (Box-folder 6/4)
        - General correspondence -- Part 1 of 8, 1977 (Box-folder 6/5)
        - General correspondence -- Part 2 of 8, 1977 (Box-folder 6/6)
        - General correspondence -- Part 3 of 8, 1977 (Box-folder 6/7)
        - General correspondence -- Part 4 of 8, 1977 (Box-folder 6/8)
        - General correspondence -- Part 5 of 8, 1977 (Box-folder 6/9)
        - General correspondence -- Part 6 of 8, 1977 (Box-folder 6/10)
        - General correspondence -- Part 7 of 8, 1977 (Box-folder 6/11)
        - General correspondence -- Part 8 of 8, 1977 (Box-folder 6/12)
        - General correspondence -- Part 1 of 5, 1978 (Box-folder 6/13)
        - General correspondence -- Part 2 of 5, 1978 (Box-folder 6/14)
        - General correspondence -- Part 3 of 5, 1978 (Box-folder 6/15)
        - General correspondence -- Part 4 of 5, 1978 (Box-folder 6/16)
        - General correspondence -- Part 5 of 5, 1978 (Box-folder 6/17)
        - General correspondence, 1979 (Box-folder 6/18)
        - General correspondence, 1980 (Box-folder 6/19)
        - General correspondence, 1981 (Box-folder 6/20)
        - General correspondence -- Part 1 of 3, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 6/21)
        - General correspondence -- Part 2 of 3, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 6/22)
        - General correspondence -- Part 3 of 3, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 6/23)
        - General correspondence, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 6/24)
        - General correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 6/25)
        - General correspondence, 2002 (Box-folder 6/26)
    - DAILY FILINGS, 1969-1979; SERIES VI (Box-folder 7/1-9/9)
      - Filings, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 7/1-7/16)
      - Filings, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 8/1-8/16)
      - Filings, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 9/1-9/9)
    - CONVENTION AND CONFERENCE RECORDS, 1945-2005; SERIES VII (Box-folder 9/10-11/6)
      - Agendas, 1949-1971 (Box-folder 9/10)
      - State Convention minutes, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 9/11)
      - American Federation of Teachers Convention, 1954 (Box-folder 9/12)
      - American Federation of Teachers Convention, 1965 (Box-folder 9/13)
      - American Federation of Teachers Convention, 1966 (Box-folder 9/14)
      - American Federation of Teachers Convention, 1968 (Box-folder 9/15)
      - American Federation of Teachers Convention, 1969 (Box-folder 9/16)
      - American Federation of Teachers Convention, 1970 (Box-folder 9/17)
      - American Federation of Teachers Convention, 1971 (Box-folder 9/18)
      - American Federation of Teachers Convention, 1972 (Box-folder 9/19)
      - American Federation of Teachers Convention, 1973 (Box-folder 9/20)
      - American Federation of Teachers Convention, 1974 (Box-folder 9/21)
      - Reports on American Federation of Teachers, National Education Association, AFL-CIO conventions, 1980 (Box-folder 10/1)
      - Association of Higher Education, 1967 (Box-folder 10/2)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers convention, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 10/3)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers Convention programs, 1950-1964 (Box-folder 10/4)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers Convention resolutions, 1964 (Box-folder 10/5)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers Convention, 1965 (Box-folder 10/6)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers Convention resolutions, 1965 (Box-folder 10/7)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers Convention, 1966 (Box-folder 10/8)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers Convention resolutions, 1967 (Box-folder 10/9)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers Convention, 1968 (Box-folder 10/10)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers Convention, 1969 (Box-folder 10/11)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers convention packet, 1969 (Box-folder 10/12)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers Convention, 1970 (Box-folder 10/13)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers Convention, 1971 (Box-folder 10/14)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers Convention, 1972 (Box-folder 10/15)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers Convention proposed constitutional amendments, 1972 (Box-folder 10/16)